Theodosius Dobzhansky Papers ca.1917-1975 Mss.B.D65
American Philosophical Society
- Series I: Correspondence, ca.1920-1975; 7.5 linear feet
  - Markow, Therese Ann, 1974; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Marks, Louis S., 1971; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Marlies, Michael, 1970; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Marshack, Alexander, 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Martin, Joan, 1974; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Martinovitch, Peter U., 1974-1975; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Masing, Rosa, 1930; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Mason, Melynda, 1975; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Massey, Gerald J., 1970; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Masson and Cie, S.A., 1970-1971; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Massopust. Thomas., 1974; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Mather, Kenneth, 1970; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Mather, Wharton, 1970-1975; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Mathieu, J., 1975-1976; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Matzinger, D. F., 1975; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Mavalwala, Jamshed, 1971; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Mayr, Ernst, 1960-1975; 8 folders (Box 9)
    Evolution; History of biology, especially genetics; National Academy of Sciences -- Allard, Robert Wayne; National Academy of Sciences -- Ayala, Francisco J.; National Academy of Sciences -- Carson, Hampton L.; National Academy of Sciences -- Lewontin, Richard Charles; National Academy of Sciences -- Wallace, Bruce; Population genetics; Research support
    - Folder 1, 1960-1962; 11 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 2, 1969-1971; 10 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 3, 1972-1974; 18 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 4, 1974; 12 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 5, 1974; 8 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 6, 1974; 18 items (Box 9)
    - Folder 7, n.d.; 1 item (Box 9)
    - Folder 8, n.d.; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Mead, Robert W., 1972; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Mears, James A., 1972; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Medem, Federico, 1970; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Médioni, Jean, 1974; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Medvedev, N., 1930-1975; 17 items (Box 10)
  - Medvedev, Zhores A., 1969-1972; 3 folders (Box 10)
    Biographical and personal data; Russian politics and science -- Lysenko, Trofim Denisovich
    - Folder 1, 1968-1969; 14 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1969-1972; 12 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 3, 1969; 12 items (Box 10)
  - Meinel, Werner, 1975; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Mellen, Sydney, 1975; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Membership materials, 1976; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Menaker, Esther - Review: The Biology of Ultimate Concern, n.d.; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mendelian Society of Lund, 1970; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mendelsohn, Everett, 1969; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Meredith, William M., 1972-1973; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Merrell David, 1962; 11 items (Box 10)
  - Merriam, John Campbell, 1937; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Merriam, John R., 1973; 6 items (Box 10)
  - Metz, Charles B., 1940-1962; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Meuron-Landolt, Monique de, 1970; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Mexican trip, 1938; 3 folders (Box 10)
    Population genetics; Research support; Travel -- Mexico
    - Folder 1, 1938; 1 item (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1938; 1 item (Box 10)
    - Folder 3, 1938; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mexican trip, 1974; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Folder 1, 1974; 12 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1974; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Meyendorff, John, 1971-1972; 9 items (Box 10)
  - Miglani, G. S., 1975; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Meyer, 1938; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Donald R., 1970; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Meyer, Merle E., 1973; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Mi, M. P., 1972; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mihram, G. Arthur, 1975; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Miller, Hal, 1972; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Miller, Hugh, 1962; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mills, Loren F., 1970; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Millsaps, Knox, 1966; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Miscellany, 1973-1976; 5 folders (Box 10)
    - Folder 1, 1963; 10 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1937; 8 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 3, 1961; 8 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 4, 1961; 8 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 5, 1976; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Mitchell, Lawrence C., 1962; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mitton, Jeffry B., 1975; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Mohler, Dawson, 1973-1974; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Mohr, Otto Lous, 1938; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Monod, Jacques, 1972; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Montagu, Ashley, 1962-1974; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Montalenti, G., 1970-1972; 4 items (Box 10)
  - Moody, Paul A., 1962; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mooney, Harold, 1971; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Moore, Betty, items (Box 10)
  - Moore, John Alexander, 1970-1975; 2 folders (Box 10)
    Biological Sciences Curriculum Study; Columbia University; Evolution; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Population genetics
    - Folder 1, 1970-1975; 5 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1972-1975; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Mora, Peter Tibor, 1971; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Moree, Ray, 1972; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Morgan, Lilian V., n.d.; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Morgan, Thomas Hunt, 1927; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Moriwaki, Daigoro, 1973-1975; 7 items (Box 10)
  - Morrish, Sandra, 1975; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mothes, Kurt, 1971-1972; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Motulsky, Arno G., 1974; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mourao, Celso, 1970-1971; 4 items (Box 10)
  - MSS Educational Publishing Company, 1970; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mukherjee, R, 1970; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Mullahy, John H., 1970; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Muller, H. J., 1962; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Müntzing, Arne, 1970-1974; 1 item (Box 10)
    Publication; Russian politics and science; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Murca Pires, Joad, 1971; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Muziegin, Oleg, 1927; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Nabokov, Vladimir, 1954; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Nalepka, Wolfgang, 1971; 2 items (Box 10)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1970-1975; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Folder 1, 1970-1975; 10 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1975; 14 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 3, 1974; 3 items (Box 10)
    - Folder 4, 1971-1974; 15 items (Box 10)
  - National Council for the Social Studies, 1971; 2 items (Box 10)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1974-1975; 1 item (Box 10)
  - National Science Foundation, 1969-1970; 3 items (Box 10)
  - National Science Teachers Association, 1971; 4 items (Box 10)
  - Natural History, 1972; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Nature, 1970-1975; 10 items (Box 10)
  - Nazarov, V. I., 1975; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Neel, James V., 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Nevo, Eviatar, 1974-1975; 10 items (Box 11)
  - New American Library of World Literature, 1954-1970; 4 items (Box 11)
  - New York Entomological Society, 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - New York Times Book Review, 1971-1973; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Newell, Norman D., 1973-1975; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1937-1967; 50 items (Box 11)
  - Nilsson-Ehle, H., 1931; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Nogar, Raymond J., 1961-1962; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Noller, Harry F., 1974; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Nord, Walter, 1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Norton, W.W., and Company, 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Notes, n.d.; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Novitski, E., 1961; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Novojenov, 1966-1971; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Nowinski, Wiktor W., 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Oberlin College, 1969; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Obrebski, Steven, 1972; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Odegard, Holton P., 1970-1971; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Oglobin, A., n.d.; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Oliver, Jack E., 1969-1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Olson, David P., 1974; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Olson, Everett C., 1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Olvera, Ramírez Olga, 1975; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Oliver, Charles G., 1972; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Olinger, Chauncey G., 1972; 1 item (Box 11)
  - O'Manique, John T., 1969; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Omenn, Gilbert S., 1971; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Organ, James A., 1973; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Oro, John, 1973; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Ortega, Virgilio, 1971; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Ortiz, Eugenio, 1962; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Osborn, Frederick, 1961-1974; 7 items (Box 11)
  - Osborne, Richard H., 1970-1973; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Osman, Florence, 1961; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Otten, Charlotte M., 1972; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Otto, Gilbert F., 1971; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Padoa, Emanuele, 1936; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Page, Ellis B., 1972; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Page, J. N. M., 1972; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Paik, Yong K., 1970-1972; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Painter, John H., 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Pak, William L., 1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Palestrina, Andrea., 1970-1974; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Papers presented in honor of Dobzhansky's 70th birthday, 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Paris, Charles A., 1972; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Paris VII, 1975; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Parisi, Paolo, 1972; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Park, Thomas, 1961; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Parker, Richard B., 1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Parry, D. Wynn, 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Parry, Renée-Marie, 1970-1975; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Parsons, P. A., 1970-1973; 9 items (Box 11)
  - Parsons, Theran D., 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Pasteur, Georges, 1970-1972; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1970; 5 items (Box 11)
    - Folder 2, 1972; 13 items (Box 11)
  - Paterniani, E., 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Patterson, John Thomas, 1936-1939; 7 items (Box 11)
    Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; University of Texas
  - Pattison, Joseph, 1972; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Pattman, John, 1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Paramonov, S., 1934-1935; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Parker, Richard B., 1970; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Pavan, C., 1956-1962; 8 items (Box 11)
    Biographical and personal data; Drosophila genetics; Population genetics; Research support; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Payne, John R., 1973; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Peacocks, Arthur, 1972; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Pearson, Helen M., 1975; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Pearson, Woodring, 1971; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Peissel, Jean Claude, 1974; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Pellew, Caroline, 1940; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Pentzo-Daponte, Athena, 1971; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Perez-Salas, Santiago, 1970-1974; 10 items (Box 11)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine, 1970-1975; 17 items (Box 11)
  - Peter, Marie Thérèse, 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Peterson, Peter A., 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Petit, Claudine, 1970-1975; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1975; 9 items (Box 11)
    - Folder 2, 1970-1974; 15 items (Box 11)
  - Pfaffman Carl, 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Phaidon Press, Ltd., 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1973; 9 items (Box 11)
    - Folder 2, 1975; 13 items (Box 11)
  - Phelphs, William H., Jr., 1969; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Phillpotts, James Surtees, 1970; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Philosophy of Science, 1970-1975; 7 items (Box 11)
  - Physical Anthropology: Man's Place in Nature, 1972; 14 items (Box 11)
  - Piediscalzi, Nicholas, 1972; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Pilbeam, David, 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Pimentel, David, 1972; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Pinevich, A., n.d.; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Pipkin, Sarah B., 1970; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Pisano, Michael A., 1974; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Pittendrigh, Colin S., 1970-1972; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Placid, Br., 1974; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Plyer, Daniel B., 1973; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Policansky, David, 1970-1974; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Polivanov, Sergey, 1970-1975; 2 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1974-1975; 15 items (Box 11)
    - Folder 2, 1970-1974; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Pollitzer, William S., 1973; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Pontecorvo, G., 1970; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Popovici, Nicolae, 1973; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Potapenko, G., 1969; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Poulson, Donald F., 1972; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Powell, Jeffrey R., 1970-1975; 7 folders (Box 12)
    Ayala, Francisco J.; Brazil; Mexico; Population genetics; Publication; Research support
    - Folder 1, 1972-1973; 9 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1973-1974; 6 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 3, 1974; 13 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 4, 1974-1975; 25 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 5, 1975; 13 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 6, n.d.; 1 item (Box 12)
    - Folder 7, 1975; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Powelson, Elizabeth E., 1970-1971; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Prabhu, S. S., 1962; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Prakash, Satya, 1970-1973; 8 items (Box 12)
  - Prance, Ghillean T., 1973-1975; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Prevosti, A., 1974; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Pringle, John W. S., 1971; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Prini, Pietro, 1970; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Printed material, ca. 1976; 24 items (Box 12)
  - Prosser, C. Ladd, 1962; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Prout, Timothy, 1972; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Provine, William, 1974; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Pruxan, Anita, 1975; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Psychological Abstracts, 1972; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Psychology Today.., 1973-1974; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Punnett, R. C., 1935; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Pyati, Jagadeesh, 1972; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Quarterly Review of Biology, 1971-1975; 10 items (Box 12)
  - Quigley, Edward J., 1973; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Quinn, James H., 1973; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Ragland, Susan Garbini, 1972; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Rajasekarasetty, M., 1972; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Rasmusen, B. A., 1974; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Raven, Peter H., 1973-1974; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Ray, James D., Jr., 1972; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Ray-Chaudhuri, S., 1970-1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Rayner, S. A., 1970-1975; 12 items (Box 12)
  - Rebert Charles S., 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Redden, David R., 1973; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Reed, Edward, 1975; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Reich, Warren T., 1975; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Reichel-Dolmatoff, Geraldo, 1969; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Reitmeister, Louis A., 1970; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Remington, Charles L., 1971; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Rensch, Bernhard, 1970-1975; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Reprint mailing list, 1971; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Reynolds, John H., 1973; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Reynolds, Peter C., 1970-1974; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Rhoades, Donald H., 1974; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Richard, G., 1975; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Richards, Jim, n.d.; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Richardson, Ralph W., 1973; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Richardson, Richard H., 1970-1973; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Richmond, Charles, 1973; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Richmond, Rollin C., 1970-1975; 8 folders (Box 12)
    Ayala, Francisco J.; Invitations; Lewontin, Richard Charles; Muller, Hermann Joseph; Population genetics; Powell, Jeffrey R.; Publication; Rockefeller Foundation; Venezuela
    - Folder 1, 1970-1971; 5 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1971-1972; 12 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 3, 1973; 22 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 4, 1973; 14 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 5, 1973; 10 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 6, 1975; 1 item (Box 12)
    - Folder 7, 1975; 2 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 8, 1975; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Richter, Curt, 1962; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Riggan, George A., 1972; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Riggs, Arad, 1970; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Rimsky-Korsakov, M., 1934; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Ringo, John M., 1973-1974; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Rio-Jelliffel, R., 1971-1972; 6 items (Box 12)
  - Roberts, H. Radclyffe, 1970-1971; 8 items (Box 12)
  - Robertson, Alan, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Robertson, Forbes W., 1970; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Robinson, David, 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1934-1974; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Folder 1, 1973; 9 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1934; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Rockefeller University, 1967-1971; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Folder 1, 1971; 1 item (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1967-1970; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Rockwell, Robert, 1970-1974; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Root, Roscoe B., 1973; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Rosenzweig, M. L., 1974; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Rothchild, Miriam Lane, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Rothen, Alexandre, 1970; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Roy, Rustum, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Royal Anthropological Institute, 1970; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Royal Entomological Society of London, 1961; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Royal Society of London, 1971; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Roze, J. Arnold, 1975; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Ruben, Laurens N., 1973-1974; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Rudkin, George T., 1971; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Ruffie, Jacques, 1971-1975; 8 items (Box 12)
  - Rush, Kenneth, 1975; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Sagan, Carl, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Salceda, Victor Manuel, 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 12)
    Drosophila genetics; Mexico; Population genetics; Research support
    - Folder 1, 1974-1975; 9 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1973; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Sargent, Theodore D., 1974; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Sanday, Peggy R., 1 item (Box 12)
  - Sanderson, K. E., 1971; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Sanghri, Lalit D., 1970; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Sankaranarayanan, K., 1971; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Saura, Anssi, 1972-1974; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Savostin, Peter, 1970; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Scarr-Salapatek, Sandra, 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 12)
    Behavioral genetics, IQ; Ethical issues
    - Folder 1, 1975; 11 items (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1973-1975; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Schaffer, Henry E., 1972; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Scharloo, W., 1974; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Scheer, Bradley T., 1975; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Scheffler, Harold W., 1974; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Scheinfeld, Amram, 1963-1973; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Schimke, Robert T., 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Schindler, Dali, 1971; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Schmalhausen, I. I. (Ivan Ivanovich), 1930; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Schmemann, Alexander, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Schmitt, Francis O., 1971; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Schmitz-Moorman, Karl, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Schnell, F. W., 1970; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Schocken Books Inc., 1974; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Schrader, Franz, 1933-1940; 14 items (Box 12)
  - Schreiber, M., 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Schulzer, Michael, 1971; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Schwarz, A. L., 1968-1973; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Schwartz, Alan W., 1972; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Schweber, Miriam Schurin, 1974; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Science (periodical), 1971-1974; 8 items (Box 13)
  - Science Year, 1969-1970; 8 items (Box 13)
  - Scientia, 1970; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Scossiroli, R., 1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Scott, J. P., 1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Scowcroft, W. R., 1971; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Scribners, Charles, Sons, 1965-1971; 11 items (Box 13)
  - Scudder, G. G. E., 1970-1971; 7 items (Box 13)
  - Sebastiani C., Federico L, 1973; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Seeger, Raymond J., 1970; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Segal, Robert, 1974; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Segre, Beniamino, 1971; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Seiger, Marvin B., 1970; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Seitz, Frederick, 1970-1971; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Selander, Robert K., 1973; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Serebrowsky, A. S., 1929; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sessions, George, 1974-1975; 6 items (Box 13)
  - VII Congreso Cientifico Americano, 1935-1938; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Seyffert, W, 1970; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Shack, William A., 1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Shackman, Arthur O., n.d.; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sheldon, Bruce L., 1961; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sheldon, Eleanor Bernert, 1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Sheppard, Phillip M., 1961-1971; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Shiekh, El Shiekh Mohamed El, 1975; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Shinn, Roger L., 1971-1974; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Shockley, William, 1970; 5 items (Box 13)
  - Shropshire, W., Jr., 1971; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Shtohryn, Dmytro M., 1975; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sigma Xi, 1928-1962; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sills, David L, 1971; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Simon, Harold J., 1962; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Simon, Mike, 1975; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Simons, Elwyn L., 1972; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Simpson, George Gaylord, 1957-1974; 2 folders (Box 13)
    Biographical and personal data; Evolution; History of biology, especially genetics; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Publication
    - Folder 1, 1973-1974; 17 items (Box 13)
    - Folder 2, 1975-1972; 18 items (Box 13)
  - Singer, Ronald, 1970; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Singer, S. J., 1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Singh, Shri B. N., 1970; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Sioli, Harald, 1970; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Siotis, Narcos, 1969-1970; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Siverzev family, n.d.; 5 items (Box 13)
  - Skolimowski, Henryk, 1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Slobodchikoff, C. N., 1971; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Smedes, Lewis B., 1974; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Smirnov, E., 1969; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Smith, Emil L., 1973; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Smith, T. L., 1961; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Smith, Vincent E., 1971; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1961; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sobelman, Max, 1971; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Sobels, F. H., 1970-1974; 5 items (Box 13)
  - Society for the Study of Human Biology, 1970-1975; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Society for the Study of Humane Genetic Applications, 1973; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Sokal, Robert R, 1972-1973; 5 items (Box 13)
  - Sokoloff, Alexander, 1962-1970; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Solar, Eduardo del, 1973-1974; 7 items (Box 13)
  - Solberg, Richard A., 1970; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Solmo, Eva, n.d.; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sondhi, K. C., 1971; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Sonneborn, Tracy M., 1968; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sonnenblick, B., 1970; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sorsa, Marja and Veikko, 1971; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Souelé, Michael, 1975; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Soyfer, V. N., 1971-1973; 8 folders (Box 13)
    - Folder 1, 1971-1972; 1 item (Box 13)
    - Folder 2, 1973-1975; 5 items (Box 13)
    - Folder 3, n.d.; 4 items (Box 13)
    - Folder 4, n.d.; 2 items (Box 13)
    - Folder 5, n.d.; 1 item (Box 13)
    - Folder 6, n.d.; 1 item (Box 13)
    - Folder 7, n.d.; 1 item (Box 13)
    - Folder 8, n..d.; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Sperlich, Diether., 1971-1975; 19 items (Box 13)
  - Spiegel, Melvin, 1973; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Spett, Georgi J., 1930-1972; 7 items (Box 13)
  - Spiegel, Der, 1974; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Spiess, Eliot B., 1961-1975; 2 folders (Box 13)
    Population genetics; Publication; Research support; Weisbrot, David
    - Folder 1, 1961-1971; 5 items (Box 13)
    - Folder 2, 1972-1975; 15 items (Box 13)
  - Spieth, Herman T., 1970-1974; 7 items (Box 13)
  - Spieth, Philip T., 1971-1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Spoehr, H. A., 1934; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Spofford, Janice B., 1973; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Spriggs, Darrell L., 1971-1972; 8 items (Box 13)
  - Springer, Konrad F., 1970; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Spuhler, J. N., 1970-1972; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Stanfield, Boris, 1974-1975; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Staples, John H., 1973; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Starr, Louis M., 1974; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Stebbins, Barbara, 1974-1975; 9 items (Box 13)
  - Stebbins, G. Ledyard, 1961-1975; 3 folders (Box 13)
    Evolution; History of biology, especially genetics; Publication; Travel -- Chile; Travel -- France
    - Folder 1, n.d.; 1 item (Box 13)
    - Folder 2, 1961-1973; 18 items (Box 13)
    - Folder 3, 1973-1975; 16 items (Box 13)
  - Stebbins, Robert C., 1961-1962; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Steinbach, H. Burt, 1961; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Stent, Gunther, 1972; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Stephens, Stanley G., 1970; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Stern, Curt, 1975; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Stern, Herbert, 1970; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Stiers, Vern, 1972; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Still, Joseph W., 1974; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Stinson, Harry T., Jr., 1970-1971; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Stockard, C. R., 1936; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Stocker, Ann J., 1971; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Stone, Wilson S., 1961-1962; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Stonehouse Press, 1973; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Strasser, Hans, 1972; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Streisinger George, 1961; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Strelnikov, Iv, 1971; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Strickberger, Monroe W., 1970-1974; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Stroun, Maurice, 1974; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Stubbs, Hans, 1975; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Sturtevant, Alfred H., 1940, n.d.; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Suomalainen, Esko, 1969-1975; 14 items (Box 14)
  - Suomalainen Tiedeakatemia, 1972; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Surget, Larry and Sheilah, 1971; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Susin, Angelo Madalozzo, 1962; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Sussman, Marvin B., 1975; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Sutt, Toomas, 1970; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Sved, John, 1969-1975; 6 items (Box 14)
  - Swain, Donald C., 1973; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Swenson, K. G., 1972-1973; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Syracuse University, 1967; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Szarski, Henryk, 1972; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Taft, J. R. Corporation, 1973; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Tagiuri, Renato, 1971; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Tantawy, A. O., 1962-1973; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Tandy, Mills, 1974; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Tatum, Edward L., 1971; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Tatum, E. L. Man in the light of evolutionary biology lecture, ca. 1971; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Taylor, Charles, 1975; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Taylor, Jeremy, 1974; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Taylor, John D., 1971; 1 item (Box 14)